{"data":[{"question":"Mark: \"My friend Gary has found a new job in the music business.\"     -> Mark said .........................................in the music business.\n","answer":"his friend Gary had found a new job","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Judy: \"I have already written this paragraph four times.\"     -> Judy complained that ................................four times.\n","answer":"she had already written that paragraph","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Freddy: \"I cannot continue to depend on my wife.\"     -> Freddy was sorry that ............ to depend on his wife.\n","answer":"he couldn't continue","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Peter: \"I will not stop until this factory is shut down.\"     -> Peter announced that .....................................................\n","answer":"he would not stop until that factory was shut down","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Jonathan: \"I don't think so.\"    -> Jonathan said ..........................\n","answer":"he didn't think so","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Her boyfriend told her: \"You have bought yourself a lovely new dress.\"     -> Her boyfriend told her ..............................................................\n","answer":"she had bought herself a lovely new dress.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Muriel: \"All I see is powder.\"     -> Muriel told us .....................\n","answer":"all she saw was powder","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"The postman: \"I think it is from America.\"     -> The postman said ............................\n","answer":"he thought it was from America.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"My friends: \"We want to leave at once.\"     -> My friends told me ..........................\n","answer":"they wanted to leave at once","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Paul: \"I don't like my new flat.\"     -> Paul said ...................\n","answer":"he didn't like his new flat","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"}]}